# **ANTONY BUDIANTO**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER AND OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTOR



# **PROFILE**

Name: Antony Budianto DOB: August 8th, 1993 From: Pontianak, Indonesia

## **EDUCATION**

**Binus University**Bachelor degree of Information
Systems major
2015

#### **SKILLS**

#### **Technical skills**

- HTML, CSS, JS, TypeScript
- React platform (Web, Native, VR)
- Angular JS, Angular
- Jest, Webpack
- NodeJS, Golang
- Git, Jenkins + Travis CI, Docker

#### Soft skills

- Team-player, fast learner
- · Languages: English, Indonesia

#### **SUMMARY**

A software engineer and open source contributor with 4+ years experience on software development, web design and development, git, writing unit and end-to-end tests, deployment and setup CI server. Actively contributing to open source and listed as one of the top 10 JavaScript GitHub developer in Indonesia by git-awards.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Tokopedia | Frontend Engineer**

Sep 2017 - present

- Developing and maintaining frontend of Tokopedia Fintech products (Mitra Toppers, Personal Loan, Credit Card, Insurance, Mutual Funds, Gold, and more)
- Building CLI toolkit to standardize frontend tooling across current/ upcoming Tokopedia Fintech products which results in reusability, maintainability, and productivity

#### **GDP Labs | Sr. Software Development Engineer**

Sep 2016 - Aug 2017

• Developed HR platform web apps using Angular 2

# **GDP Labs | Software Development Engineer**

Developed vehicle insurance enterprise application using Angular JS

#### Binus University | Network Administrator

Sep 2014 - Aug 2015

Sep 2015 - Aug 2016

 Cloning images for software lab computers, ensure networks running well, patching, calibration, maintenance, and develop various network-based applications

#### Binus University | Teaching Assistant

Sep 2013 - Aug 2014

Teach various programming languages in software lab classes

#### **PROJECT**

#### **CRA Universal**

https://github.com/antonybudianto/cra-universal

- Create React App companion for universal app
- No eject, Zero config, Full HMR
- Supports server-side rendering with code-splitting

#### Gitfun

https://gitfun-web.herokuapp.com

- Simple GitHub client browser and repository summary
- Available on Web and Android (React Native)

Generated using https://github.com/antonybudianto/react-resume